Good morning everyone.  The time is
seven in the morning.
I'm starting this cloudy autumn day with a simple routine
.  I fix my hair and
choose some jewelry if possible.
As I got older, I
had a serious acne problem.  That's why
I did
n't like my morning routine at all, because I had to look in the mirror.    I want to
hug the past me and
tell me to be patient, everything will change with time
.  I'll share
how I improved my skin
and my
personal
routine in the
last part of this video for those who are interested
.
Another thing
is, I really like
these jars that I use to hide my things
, as well as
this
Japanese-style
flower pot that I found in second-hand stores
.
I've been really liking some
new perfumes lately
.
Applying them is
my
favorite part of my morning routine.
I
love scents.  They have a
very positive
impact on me
.
Today I
woke up very early
because I wanted to prepare some ingredients before starting my
important work
.  I especially wanted to make
my
favorite
spice cake
.  Especially in
the fall
,
I
love the flavors of vanilla, cloves, cinnamon, and nutmeg, and this
cake has
them all.
It tastes like a gingerbread
man
and is great to
eat during this time of the winter season
.
Now all I have to do is
control myself from tasting the batter before I put the cake in the oven
.    When the
cake
was finished, it was still
delicious, even though it was unfortunately a little overbaked.    As
it was
cooling down
, I went out with Eiger to look for
seasonal
decorations
.
Snow berries are
very abundant right now
.  They were
so
pretty to look at, even though I
couldn't eat them
, I thought I'd bring some home to make an arch
.  For me, yarrow
and snow
berries are
symbols of strength and peace.
I
love having icons like that in my house.  They remind me to brave the coming
winter, the
new
year,
and make my dreams come
true
.    I
decided to decorate my spice cake with snow berries right then and there
.  But don't worry
, I didn't let
anyone
eat them.
They are just
for decoration
.  But
sometimes it seems to me that it's
better to prioritize beauty over practicality
.
It's even
better when decorating sweets like this, especially for festivals.
Hello everyone.  I hope you have a
great week
.  I would now like to
change the subject a little and share with you about my
personal
routine
, because
a lot of
people
ask about this, and
it makes me very
happy
.
Thank you.  Thank you for your
kind words
.    I wanted
to share with you a very simple routine I've had since I made a video about self-care about a year ago
.  My routine has
become even simpler,
as I am just now dealing with the last signs of the skin problems of my
teens and
young adulthood
.
My sister and
I both suffered from
a lot of skin
problems while growing up
.  I used to have severe
cystic
acne
that
would spread all over my face.
It made me feel very low
.    It seems
easy to take skin problems lightly
because they
seem like a small matter,
but in
reality, it is
very
difficult to live with constant pain and discomfort when you have skin problems.  It's
not just a matter of appearance.
For skin care,
I use a
regular
moisturizer
and other
creams prescribed by my dermatologist
.
I will give you the
details below
, they have
completely
transformed my skin.
When I was very young, I
tried using Accutane
, but I had a
severe
reaction to it
.  That would have been
very scary
.
So, that's
not a suitable option for me.
But yes,
I
got here with lifestyle changes, especially stress reduction, and advice from dermatologists many years ago, as well as advice from amazing experts on YouTube.
I have
come a long way.
So,
no matter what skin problem you are suffering from,
be patient, it
takes time.    When it
comes to cosmetics, I
like to keep it simple,
but
I have a
lot of fun using them
.  I
love glitter, so I
sometimes
put a little glitter on my eyes
.  I am using these
perfume
oils
.
I
also have another one from the Mythology Candle Company
.  This is
taken from Perfume Oil Expressions.
None of this is
sponsored
.  I wanted to share with you that these are
my
favorite
perfumes
.  I always
used spray perfumes, which
had a lot of alcohol in them.  In my
case
, I found that these last a very
long time
, that a
very
small
amount is
enough,
and that you do
n't need to reapply them
.    Let me
tell you about some of my favorite scents.  I have
many
.  I
mostly like floral
scents
or scents that are a bit more
cheerful and
fresh
.    I
also want to tell you that I actually wear glasses
.  I don't wear them when in front of the camera
,
because
sometimes the
light reflection on them is
too much
.
So I
wear glasses.  I
also have contact lenses.
Yes, that is also
part of my daily routine.  If I didn't
wear contact lenses
, I would wear glasses
.  If you're also someone who doesn't
look right
,
you're welcome to our club.
Many
people
ask me about my hair care routine.
It's very
simple
.  I
mix leftover conditioner with water and
pour it into a spray bottle,
detangle my hair and
spray it every morning
so my
hair
stays fresh all day.  Or on
some days when
I don't have the
patience to take care of that much hair
,
I
comb all my hair back,
then it
looks a little straighter.
My hair is so
thick that it's
enough for two people,
it's so
thick and
curly
.  Although it may
look
good
, to be
honest, there are
many different
things in my hair
.  A while
ago when I was at the
grocery
store
, a
woman
came up behind me and
told me that a bee was stuck in my hair.  That
poor bee
was trying hard to get out of my hair
, but the hair was
too thick for
it to
get out.
I am very
sad.
I took that
bee outside into the
garden
,
hoping it was okay
.  What a day!
That's a nightmare.
Yes, it may
seem strange to talk about these things, but
I
think it will be very helpful to others
.  I wish you all a
very good week
.  The
most
interesting
thing about you will never be your outward
appearance
.  I send
my love to all of you
.
I will be there.